<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SimpleCalculator</string>
    <string name="bmw">The RR is now even more focused and more precisely geared towards pure performance. For those who increasingly demand more. More from themselves. More each lap. And more from their RR. Simply put: #NeverStopChallenging. Leading the way is a matter of millimeters, especially in the circles the RR has always been a part of. That’s why we have streamlined and evolved the RR where it matters most: from the new steering angle sensor with Brake Slide Assist and Slide Control as well as the integration of M components and improvements to the electronics and crucial processes for modifying the bike for the race track. And all this with a clear goal in mind – claiming the pole position over and over again.</string>
    <string name="kawasaki">You can beat all opponents, but there is always a challenge you still have to face, the one within yourself. For those like you who rise to any challenge, we have developed the bike that a true champion deserves. The new Ninja ZX-10R and Ninja ZX-10RR have what it takes to win: all new aerodynamic body with integrated winglets, small and light LED headlights, TFT Colour instrumentation, and Smartphone connectivity plus updates derived from Kawasaki Racing Team World Superbike expertise. Now that you have the definitive race focused Ninja, Face Yourself. The Ninja ZX-10RR was designed to win races with as little fuss as possible. In the capable hands of Kawasaki racers, the Ninja ZX-10RR is designed to deliver legendary performance.</string>
    <string name="yamaha">With its latest generation unveiled last 2015 at the centennial EICMA motorcycle show, the Yamaha YZF R1 1000 is a sport bike which is sure to deliver ample power coupled with expensive components such as for that extraordinary riding experience. Locally, this beautiful beast can be had in only one ABS variant retailing at P1,099,000. Color options include Black Raven and Race Blue. As mentioned in the previous paragraph, it does get a number of expensive components which contributes to its overall dynamics including magnesium wheels and a carbon fiber bodywork. It also gets the basics such as LED headlamp, LED tail lamp, and digital gauges. Powering this two wheeler is a mighty 998cc 4-stroke, liquid-cooled, DOHC engine which churns out a healthy 200 hp and 112 Nm of torque. This mill is then paired with a six-speed manual. As for safety and security features, The Yamaha YZF R1 1000 comes standard with Anti-lock Braking System (ABS), traction control, slipper clutch, immobilizer, an alarm system, and a pass switch.</string>
</resources>